All right, you guys, this is one of
the craziest cribs I've ever seen in my life.
I can't even call this a house.
This is a little compound, but let's
see if we can get some free game.
I wanted to open it up to you, just
a few questions for your advice to the younger generation.
Sure, I'll take it.
Thank you, sir. I appreciate that.
Yeah, you want to come in?
Yeah, thank you.
Awesome.
How long have you lived in Houston for?
Got here in 1982.
Houston, Texas is the number eight city
in the world with the most millionaires.
Today, we're going to be asking multimillionaire
homeowners in Houston how they became wealthy.
All right, guys, we just got to
our first neighborhood out here in River Oaks.
We're going to be going up to these doors, asking
these multimillion dollar homeowners how they were able to become wealthy.
Let's go in and see if
we can ask them some questions.
It's crazy, man, because we're not just anywhere.
We're out in Texas, and you know how these Texas
people are about just going up to their places and solicitors.
And even though we're not soliciting, we're really
just trying to do this for a good cause.
You got to be very careful, because some people not take
it the right way, going under the door with a camera.
But we want to do our best
to get this content for you guys.
All right, guys, we're here at
our first house in Houston, Texas.
We're going to go up and ask this multimillion
dollar homeowner how they were able to become successful.
Hello.
Hi.
Question for you.
Wanted to know if we could ask
you or someone to add a few questions.
Yeah, sure.
I mean, where are you originally from?
I'm originally from Pakistan.
And what industry did you ultimately pursue a career in?
Anesthesia.
I'm a physician.
Oh, my God.
My journey is very, very long.
Because I was a physician in my country.
And then when I came here, I had
to do all the licensing exams all over again.
But, you know, the beauty about America is if you
put your passion into something that you really want to do,
people recognize that.
And no matter what, they bring you up.
What has been the most amount of money
that you ever made in a single year?
I've made, like, seven figures plus, yeah.
And what would you say is the best
financial advice that you've ever received throughout your lifetime?
You know, somebody once told me that the seventh wonder,
the fourth wonder of the
world is the power of compounding.
So that one dollar that you put into your 401k as
a young person, when you retire, you will see the effect.
So I always tell my kids, the minute you get a
job, open your 401k account and put some money in it.
And my final question for you, for someone
who is, I guess, pursuing healthcare and medicine today,
it takes a lot to be able to work your way up
and make seven figures in any field, but let alone in medicine.
It's competitive.
What's the biggest thing that really made you stand
out in that industry that is a competitive industry?
That's honestly.
It's 90% hard work.
You know, the cream always rises to the top.
For 10 years, I worked every
Christmas, every Thanksgiving, holidays, nights, days.
You get the reward in the end.
Thank you so much for your time.
I really appreciate that.
I loved your answer.
All right.
Thank you very much.
Thank you so much.
That was our first house
that we went up to today.
She's killing it.
Over seven figures in a single year as a physician.
Came from Pakistan.
Now lives in the United States.
I loved her answer talking about compounding interests.
But guess what?
She said, that's the seventh wonder.
Let's go find the eighth
wonder and find this next house.
Hey, sir.
Quick question for you, sir.
Are you the homeowner?
Yeah.
I would love to just ask you a
few quick questions on how you became successful.
No, I don't think I'm going to do that.
No worries, sir.
Have a great day, though.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Even though we started the day off with a win,
we had no idea what was coming
our way over the next five hours.
Country, but I'm based in Austin.
Just asking beautiful homeowners a
few questions on their advice
to the younger generation.
I have no interest in it.
No worries.
Have a nice day.
Trying to become successful one day.
No, have a good one.
I'm sorry.
I don't have any interest.
No worries, sir.
Have a nice day.
Thank you.
Hey, he didn't have any interest,
but he would have had interest
because he would have gotten a million views.
But all that matters is that you're
liked and you subscribe to this video
and go follow the School of Hard Knocks everywhere.
All right, you guys.
We just pulled up to an
absolute compound out here in Houston, Texas.
We're going to go up and
see if we can talk to them.
But it's going to be hard because it's gated.
We'll see if they can come down.
I'm sorry.
We can't talk right now.
OK, no worries.
Have a nice day, sir.
Couldn't talk right now.
It sucks.
It's hard.
You know, a lot of these guys
are super busy people, very high class people.
So it's going to be hard to
get a lot of these people's times.
But all we can do is keep
going and go get the next one.
This is one of the craziest
cribs I've ever seen in my life.
I can't even call this a house.
This is a little compound.
But let's see if we can get some free game.
How you doing, sir?
Just asking beautiful homeowners a
few questions on their advice
on how they became successful for the younger generation.
Thought you had one of
the most beautiful homes in Houston.
Wanted to ask you just a few questions.
Sure, I'll take it.
Thank you, sir.
I appreciate that.
Yeah, you want to come in?
Yeah, thank you.
Awesome.
Cool.
What industry did you ultimately pursue a career in?
Oh.
I've actually had only one job in my life.
I started out 17 years
old, working part time at McDonald's,
going to college.
And I just stayed with it.
And that created all this.
And my children have their own restaurants as well.
So you start in open McDonald's?
Well, you become a franchisee.
So how many McDonald's have
you opened throughout your career?
Well, that's a bigger number.
We currently have 50.
And my kids have 19.
That's incredible.
And how have you really
been able to scale your business?
A lot of people, they'll have a great idea,
they'll start a business.
But they struggle to scale.
That's the edge.
That's the energy that a franchise will give you.
Of course, you have to
have some experience and the will
to work hard and get it done.
That's really about perseverance.
You've got to be with the right franchise too.
Right.
You're the ones that fail.
Throughout your career, what's the best financial advice
you've ever received throughout your lifetime?
Well, I'd give the same advice to anybody else.
I give to my kids.
And advice I followed, I lived with enough money
just to make ends meet.
And all the rest of
it went to pay down debt.
Once you get out of debt, you become much freer
in a lot of things.
And I mean all kinds of debt.
Car debt, house debt, business debt, of course, comes first.
What's been your secret to sales as a business?
McDonald's is a formula.
So the advertising is nationwide as well as local.
And I've done a lot of
committee work on the national level.
And that's been my whole career.
And it's been great.
It's a great business.
It's hard working, very difficult.
But you stay with it, you'll get the rewards.
Final question for you.
Any last words, any advice to the younger generation
that's aspiring to own a multimillion dollar house
like this?
Well, this didn't come overnight.
Let me just say that.
We've been here 12 years now.
And we built it from scratch.
And it's our vision.
We collect a lot of art.
And that's the story.
We just enjoy.
And I want to pay attention to it.
And I want to pass
on the wealth to other folks.
Thank you so much for your time.
I really appreciate that.
Thank you.
It means so much for you taking the time
to answer some questions for us.
Thank you, sir.
I mean, that's one of the most insane houses
that I've ever been in my entire life.
My man owns McDonald's all over the country.
Let us come into his home.
Did you guys see the artwork in there?
Did you guys see that house?
I mean, that's got to
be one of the craziest experiences
I've ever had running this channel.
Look at this house right here.
Show them the house real quick.
Part of the game of
going up to these people's houses
is you've got to make a good first impression.
You're asking these people for the time
to knock on their doors.
You're bothering their day.
You have got to sell yourself
in the first five to 10 seconds
that you get there.
Making a good impression is super important.
And we do just that
at the School of Hard Knocks.
All right, you guys.
Just look at this crib right here.
I don't know what this person had
to do to be able to own this place.
But regardless, we're going to go and find out.
Hello?
Yeah, can I help you?
We wanted to know if we could just ask you
a few quick questions on your advice to the younger
generation and how you became successful.
OK.
Go ahead.
Could we do it in person?
Or if we could do it over there?
It's totally up to you.
Well, I'm not at home.
I'm in California.
Oh, OK.
Yeah, I guess.
What did you do for a living?
I'm a physician.
What's the best financial advice that you ever received
throughout your lifetime?
The most important thing probably
is to not overextend yourself.
So you have to live below your means.
And if you can live below your means,
I think you could get
during bad times, you're pretty safe.
But if you don't live below your means, what happens
is you're going to have
expenses that are beyond your capacity
in bad times.
Final question is, you know, you've
really got one of the most beautiful houses
I've ever seen in Houston.
And to own a multimillion dollar home like this,
it obviously took some incredible hard work.
So maybe any last message for the younger generation
on how they can really become successful,
regardless of their industry?
I think what happens is
people look for the easy way.
And if you look for the easy way,
you're never going to find it.
Thank you, sir.
Have a great day.
My man wasn't here, but he was nice enough
to do a five-minute interview.
He's out in California right now,
and he took the time to actually join the call
and talk to us while we
were at his house in Houston.
Second physician of the day, but that's crazy, man.
The real gain that he gave.
Don't overextend.
Don't over-leverage yourself.
Get your head in the game.
Put your head down, and don't
look for the easy way out.
Let's keep going.
All right, you guys.
This house is listed at over $36 million on Zillow.
We're going to go see if someone's home
and figure out how they were
really able to own this house.
How you doing?
Good.
How about yourself, sir?
Kind of ask, like, what'd you do for a living?
I used to own and operate automobile dealerships
in Houston, Texas.
Yeah, I owned Champion Ford, Texan Ford, Texan Lincoln,
Mercury, Zuzu, and a number of other stores.
And then I sold my company to AutoNation
and ran AutoNation for about a year.
A year and a half until I basically resigned
and then started doing some investment projects
and other things like that.
So I started to buy my own stores.
If you were to go back
to when you started your first business,
what's the number one thing
you wish you would have known?
I wish I had an opportunity to learn more
about operational businesses at
school, at the business school
at the University of Texas,
and really attended a class that
dealt with what you're going
to deal with as a young
entrepreneur when you go and start
to operate your own business.
You're not going to do it by the textbook.
You're not going to read it.
You're not going to really learn that in school itself.
You're going to have to basically get
with somebody who's willing to mentor you
and take the time to instruct you on everything
you've got to look at.
The company I went to work
for after I left Ford Motor Company
in 1979 was broke within three months.
And it went bankrupt, almost bankrupt.
And we salvaged it to become
the number one Ford dealer in truck
sales in the country in a year and a half.
We did that because we really organized a team
to come together on one
what I call biggest thing ever
in my life is a rally.
The motivational point.
But I want to talk about something just
Here's what's happening at that stage.
When you sit in front of a bunch of people
and you've got to make a payroll of $150,000 a week,
$400,000 a week, a million dollars a week, you know,
and you've got other families relying on
you as the leader of that organization
to try to achieve that and
make that accomplishment come true for everybody,
you've got to have that rallying point.
You've got to have that motivational point.
But there's one thing you guys
need to learn coming out of school.
You don't have to be the smartest guy, okay?
Yes, sir.
You don't have to be the biggest guy.
You don't have to be the fastest guy.
All you have to do is
be the best guy you can be,
and you can be that by
outworking anybody else in that organization.
You learn to outwork everybody else, and I
promise you good things will happen for you.
Wow.
Hey, my man showed up to the gate and just dropped
a five-minute bomb on us on how he was able to.
He sold his company to AutoNation, ran
multiple businesses in the automobile industry for years.
This guy's a mogul.
Look at his crib.
Look at him going back in there.
You've got to show him.
重來
industry did you pursue a career in? Well, I
was a professional touring musician. Then when I turned
40, I became a chef and owned restaurants and
run restaurants. And now I cook for high profile
clients. That's amazing. The food and
hospitality restaurant business can be very competitive.
What's the biggest thing you've implemented
throughout your skillset as a business owner
to really stand out? Your biggest asset is your
staff. Treat them like gold and they'll treat you
like gold. It's a team effort. You can't do it
on your own. You got to treat your staff well
and they'll bend over backwards for you. So I
guess I'll kind of end on by asking you,
for somebody coming out of school today, what's
your best advice to someone starting out in the
real world? How can they really put their
head down, become successful and earn six figures?
Work hard, play harder. How can you play harder?
It's all about balance. You got to make time for
it. If you burn yourself out and you let life
pass you by, sure, you have a lot of money,
but don't take that with you. Take experiences with
you. What kind of cigar do we have right now?
Oliva V. Oliva V? Have a good one, man. Thank
you so much for your time. Have a great day,
sir. Really appreciate that. It means a lot.
Thank you, sir. Hey, the only thing I regret
was not asking him for a hit of that Cuban,
but a man came through. We stopped
him on the street coming in, professional chef,
owned restaurants around Houston. Man, Houston's crazy. You
never know who you can run into out
here, but let's keep trucking. Let's go get
this next one. Okay. So what was his name?
Just type in Tillman. Okay. F-E-R-T-I-T-T-A.
Hey, that's a billionaire that lives there.
Crazy. Oh my God, he owns the rocket.
Are you serious? Yes. Security guard came
to the door, asked what we were doing,
trying to get an interview. He said, you
can look up it. His name's Tillman Fertitta. This
is the owner of the Houston Rockets that
lives here. Are you serious? He's a billionaire. He
owns Landry's Inc. and the Houston Rockets. I
literally today said, what if we found the
owner of the Houston Rockets now? He's gone
home, but we found his house. That's fucking incredible.
His net worth is $8.4 billion. My man's out
here is pulling back into his driveway with a Rolls
Royce. We're going to go and try and snag
this interview real quick. See what the hell this guy
did on how he was able to own a rocket. I'm
going to go and snag this interview real quick. See what
the hell this guy did on how he was
able to own a Rolls Royce out in Houston, Texas.
Excuse me, bro. Question for you. This is
your Rolls Royce? Yeah. My friends and I,
we started a channel in Austin, Texas. We grew
up to 1.5 million followers. Is that cool? We
ask you a few questions? Yeah, sure. That's fine.
Okay. I guess my first question for you is,
man, you're having a conversation with a young
kid, 20 years old. He's fresh out of college.
He wants to get serious about becoming financially
free. What is the 60-second blueprint that it took
for you to be able to own a Rolls Royce?
Oh, man. It took about 10 years for me to
really figure out business and how to
become successful in business. 60 seconds might
be tough, but I would say, if I had to sum
it up, is you have to always want to learn. It's not
just going to come easy. If you think it's going
to come easy, you're not going to get it. But if
you want it and you're willing to learn and
you're willing to work, then you'll find out whatever it
takes to get it. But if you want, we
can talk more about business in general and elaborate a
little bit more because I think it's going to be
hard to explain it in 60 seconds. Would that be
cool? Could we come in for a little bit? Yeah,
if you guys want. I got a few minutes. All right,
let's get it. Let's go, guys. Yeah. So if you
guys want to come on in, there's a mic for me.
Yeah. You guys came prepared. Welcome to my house.
You can tell cars are my thing. I do
love cars. Yeah. Could you kind of explain what
cars you own right now? Yeah, I'm building a house
for a bigger garage because I can't hold them all
here. So a lot of them are at my warehouse. But
you saw the Rolls Royce. We've got a Lamborghini
Urus SUV with a wide body kit. I love classic
cars. So you see a 1972 Chevelle with a 454
big block in it. Over here, you see a red Ferrari
458, naturally aspirated, one of my favorite cars.
But this is definitely my childhood dream car. So
this is the Lamborghini Diablo. I have
the poster of this car on my
bedroom. I have the poster of this car on my
bedroom. I have the poster of this car on my bedroom. I
have the poster of this car on my bedroom. I have the
wall when I was a kid. So to drive it and to
own it, to me, is like a dream come true. But come on
and we'll talk a little bit more. So like
what industry did you ultimately pursue a career in?
Yes, I became a doctor and then I specialized
in emergency medicine. So I handle all traumatic and
medical emergencies that would come into an ER.
And now how long have you been an entrepreneur
for? So I started relatively early. My first
year after graduating is when I started turning the
way too long. I think a lot of
people will say, oh, no, let me wait.
Let me wait for this. Let me wait
for that. Sometimes you have to, but sometimes you're
just stalling. You're just delaying. And you might
start saving up money. Then you're like, well,
let me buy this first. Let me buy that first.
And now you don't have the capital. But if you can
focus and just save as much as you can. Like
my first year out, I worked probably three times as
much as a normal doctor would. It was nonstop because
I knew I had to save to have enough money
to take to a bank and get a
loan to build my first facility. Throughout your lifetime,
what was the best financial advice you
ever received? You don't go for money,
but think of money as a tool, as a
tool to do something great. I think when you approach
it that way, you're always happy, even when you
don't have the money, even when you're trying to
build yourself up and become successful in business.
But if you focus on money and cars,
you're never going to be happy. And if you're
not happy, you're probably not going to have the drive
and the passion you need to get there. So never
focus on the money and think of money as a tool
to do great things.